http://scottsworld.info/privacy.html

Questions Answered by the Book of Mormon
101 Answers from the Book of Mormon to life's great questions
Bible Prophecies of the Book of Mormon
The Challenge the Book of Mormon Makes to the World
Gospel Principles Comments and Resources index page
Apologetic
Which is the True Church?
The Bible is the Only word of God?
COME NOW, AND LET US REASON TOGETHER
Scott's Testimony of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints
Data protection
The owner of this site takes the protection of your personal data very seriously. I have https server but most of the site does not collect any personal information that it is needed.
We treat your personal data confidentially and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy.
The use of our website is possible without providing personal data. When personal information is requested (for example, name and email address on the contact form of the genealogy page or blog or email you send me), this is given voluntarily. This data will not be passed on to third parties.
We point out that sending information over the Internet is subject to security issues. Complete protection of the data from being accessed by third parties is not possible.
Cookies
This website use cookies. Cookies can not harm your computer and do not contain viruses. Cookies perform important functions in the operation of this site blog and genealogy pages. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer by your browser.
Most of the cookies we use are "session cookies". They are automatically deleted when you close your browser. Other cookies remain stored on your device until you delete them. These cookies allow us to recognize your browser the next time you visit and restore some of your preferences (such as your preferred language).
You can configure your browser settings so that you are informed about the setting of cookies and allow cookies only in certain cases. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.
Server log files
The host (Bluehost) of these pages automatically collects and stores information in server log files, which your browser transmits to them. These are:
Browser type and version
Operating system
Referrer URL
Host name of the accessing computer
IP address (anonymized)
Time of request
The data can not be assigned to specific persons. This data will not be merged with other data sources. We reserve the right to check this data retrospectively, if we become aware of specific indications for illegal use.
Google Analytics
The webpages of the site contain Google Analytics java script which provides data about which pages are accessed, how long and much of the same information that the server collects. This information is compiled and available to me from their websites.
Email
If you email me inquiries, your details from the email, including the contact details you provided there, will be stored in order to process the request and in case of follow-up questions. Of course, we will not pass on this data.
E-Mail Scott
[Scott's World Blog]
[Scott's World Forum]
[Cactus Wren, Scott's Weather Station]
[Genealogy, Scott's Ancestry] [Descendants of Capt.
Henry Woodward.]
[About Scott] [Scott's Testimony of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints]
[COME NOW, AND LET US REASON TOGETHER]
[God's Plan of Salvation]
[Questions Answered by the Book of Mormon]
[101 Answers from the Book of Mormon to life's great questions]
[The Challenge the Book of Mormon Makes to the World] [Bible Prophecies of the Book of Mormon]
[Which is the True Church?]
[The Bible is the Only word of God?]
[The People's Right to Bear Arms] [2nd Amendment Quotes] [Conservative Opinions]
[LDS & Genealogy Bookmarks]
[General Bookmarks] [RKBA, Political & news Bookmarks]
[Home] [E-Mail Scott] [Site Map]
[HTML help and hints] [About Scott's World Web Pages]
Links to me Scottsworld Wordpress blog
